As we all travel across the sea,
raising our voices, we take
in the beautiful blue world.
Our spirits ready to
go, everybody rejoices.
Now let's go, get the sails all unfurled.
La la la la la.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Here we are in between
the sea and the sky.
Ready now for adventure,
we're itching to try.
Get ready to roam.
So all aboard now we're set to go!
Set sail to the ocean so deep.
Ready for a truly grand adventure!
Well don't you think
that sounds really fun?
All this excitement is second to none!
As we all travel across the sea.
Raising our voices we take.
In the beautiful blue world.
Our spirits ready to go.
Everybody rejoices!
Now let's go get the sales all unfurled.
If there's something that
I just won't ever forget.
It's the way that I felt
when our journey was set.
Now I won't be scared.
As long as I keep that feeling there.
With that, let us keep up the pace!
While enjoying every
trip from place to place.
Our timid hearts get the rhythm ingrained.
So let's keep going, adventure awaits!
So many treasures await!
So now let's raise our voices in pride.
Laughing out when they are found.
With all the riches in
hand, everybody rejoices!
Party on, cause we stand tall and proud!
Life is adventurous, be
aware it's dangerous.
Who's gonna be one of us?
And a trip goes on because.
We're the pirates of the mouse.
To the west, to the east.
Gotta find my way, sail away,
all the way to one piece.
Bring all your dreams with
you now, fill the void.
In your heart, spread your wings.
And believe that you can soar.
Just let the breeze guide the way.
Till you're ready to start up once again.
Now you're ready for more.
So many treasures away.
So now let's raise our voices in pride.
Laughing out when they are found.
With all the riches in hand.
Everybody rejoices, party on.
Cause we stand tall and proud.
Hunt them down wherever they may run.
And bring them before your master.
A few miserable pirates are
no match for your strength.
Hey, could you pull it together
for once, Captain John?
At least try to live up to the
reputation you had when you were alive.
Aye, aye, sir!
On my way.
Insufferable lout.
Master M, let's get married?
Lola! Damn it!
Get over there and fight
with the other zombies!
Your commander orders you!
You have to marry me first.
Hell no!
Come on now, Lola.
Let's not be rash.
Do as your master commands
and play nice, alright?
Sure, if you marry me.
Are you insane?
I'm a human, you fool!
I'm marrying another human,
that's the end of it!
Come on, think about this for a second.
Lola, you're a warthog.
Also, you're dead and rotting.
Not exactly a match made in heaven here.
Huh?
Whoa, that was close.
Okay, let's calm down and stop touching.
And that's a marriage
certificate, isn't it?
You take that thing back
wherever you got it from.
I don't care what you're saying,
but keep moving those sexy lips.
Kiss me.
I love you, baby.
You behave!
I'm not letting some animal carcass
haunt me the rest of my life!
Bridal martial arts!
Marital bell kiss!
All right, Lola, you've
got to listen this time!
I've already found my bride.
She may have a sharp tongue
and some bothersome friends,
but at the end of the day,
she's human and she's alive?
and that's all that really matters.
You're just going to get rejected again.
Oh look she's one of the pirates
that's running amok on the island.
I'll capture her when we
capture the rest of the crew.
Not if I can help it.
I'll find her
and finish her off.
No.
Stop ruining my life.
Lola.
Hey. Kumasi.
Kumasi.
The risky brothers should be
delivering the coffin as we speak.
Pick it up from them and take it straight
to our master over at the dance hall.
Got it?
Did you hear me?
Don't just stare!
Yes. That's gross!
I told you not to talk!
I'm heading to the Straw
Head ship to clean out their
treasure collection while they're
busy with all the zombies.
Let me know if anything strange happens.
Okie Dock.
There you go.
You're much cuter when you
keep that ugly mouth shut.
Um, take care out there.
Hey, did you just mumble something at me?
Coming through with a delivery
for our master. Yep, yep, uh-huh.
Pass, we dropped it.
Oh, my, that's bad.
Whatever will the master
think if it's broken?
Oh, no, the lid came off.
What happened?
Crap, they're awake.
We're screwed.
Kill them.
Hit them to death.
Hurry, hurry.
Killing is bad.
OK, half kill them, half dead.
Usopp, Nami.
Guys, we're OK.
Wake up.
But wait, that guy, he cut us.
He must have used the back of his sword.
Looks like it rained
while we were knocked out.
The ground's a bit wet. Where are we?
All I know is we're outside now.
And those little squirrel guys dragged
us here in that coffin we were just in.
Holy crap, it is a
coffin. I didn't notice.
Aw, turds, all three
of them are awake now.
Let's book it.
We need backup. I see.
They brought us to the
back of the mansion.
I think Hogback's lab was on the top
floor, so they took us pretty far.
It's probably good we woke up when we did.
Look, behind us, there's an even
bigger building on the other side.
Huh.
I wonder what it's for.
Kind of crazy.
That huge building was here the entire
time, and we didn't even notice it.
Usopp, chopper! Hmm?
I know exactly what
this place is! Oh, yeah?
Well, let's hear it then?
Cuz I'm lost!
Look,
this is a bridge that connects one building
to the other or more like a passageway.
Passageway, it's kind of wide for that.
Don't you think there's even a forest?
Well, it's kind of a forest and
kind of a bedroom or something.
But anyway,
if they were dragging us through here
while we were passed out Then they
must have been taking us to that other
building for some reason or another!
It's probably better that we don't know.
Don't be a baby!
They were turning us into
zombies and you know it.
Then what are we waiting for?
We've got to get out of here!
Yeah, I'm not going back in that coffin!
Not so fast, guys. Huh?
Let's calm down for a second here.
We were running scared for so long, I
feel like we're forgetting something.
Think!
I don't want to think!
I want to run! I know!
My something freaky detector's
detecting something freaky!
Mine too!
Let's get out of here, Nami!
There could be zombies coming!
There was something that
Jack in the Box said.
What was it?
Sorry, suckers, but there's
no treasure in this room.
Whatever it is, it doesn't matter.
Figure it out later.
Nami, I'm scared. I know.
I'm just trying to come
up with a plan here.
I'm as scared as you are.
That's not what your eyes are saying.
Then which way are we running?
Forward or back?
That's a good question If
we head back to the mansion,
we might run into that
zombie samurai again, huh?
Yeah, but the other place might have
even tougher, even scarier guys.
Whoa!
I don't think penguins are normally
forest animals, but whatever.
Count off!
One, two, three.
Howdy, folks, they call us.
The penguin zombie duo.
Wait, that's not right.
Trio, we're a trio.
I'm the new guy. Who cares?
Not me, that's for sure.
And behind you is the rest of the crew
and what our friends the wild zombies?
Now let's meet them to a bloody!
Hurry, Usopp, fire! Fire? Huh? Burn them!
These guys are zombies too!
Special attack! Gunpowder!
Are you okay?
Behind you! Chopper! Look out!
No! Chopper!
Perhaps you should worry less about your
friends and a bit more about yourself.
Don't you dare!
Hey, stupid!
Whose side are you on, anyway?
I know you're new here,
but that girl's a pirate!
Kick her ass!
I don't care who this lady
is or where she came from.
I don't even care if I have
to disobey a master's orders.
Because even if it kills
me, I'll never kick a woman!
You got a problem with
that, then bring it on!
You piece of crap zombies!
Sanji! Anybody?
Stupid pig, just tell us where
you hit our friends already!
Come on!
Like I said before, ask all you like.
I don't know a thing!
When we get our cook back,
we're making bacon out of you.
Perhaps they were strangled, and
so they can't call out for help.
No more predictions out of you.
They're way too depressing.
Hey, wait a second.
When do we last see Zoro?
Zoro! Sanji!
Man, where did they go?
This is no time to screw around.
What's wrong with you?
Hey, everybody knows if
there's armor laying around,
you gotta put it on and wear it.
It's like fulfilling a man's dream.
What?
Oh, wow.
That's a good point.
Don't tell me when you made a body out of
iron you gave yourself a cold iron heart,
too.
I'm sorry, you're right.
Even if I have fists of iron,
that's no replacement for a
heart that's full of dreams.
Yeah, song time!
Realizing I've lost something
so precious has blown
a cold wind through the
rusty cracks of my heart.
I call this one Steel
Cyborg Traveler Blues.
I think you forgot the situation here.
Hey, there's a large
hall up ahead. Really?
Robin!
Are Usopp and the others here?
No, but take a look at this room.
We should be outside once
we pass through here.
Whoa, what is this place?
Looks like some kind of arena.
It's actually a lot more
complicated than that.
Oh, but don't worry about the details.
You'll find out soon enough since you've
conveniently walked right into our trap!
Franky!
Who is that?
A haunted suit of armor!
It must be a zombie.
It has spears piercing its body,
but it's still moving around.
So now the zombies are arming themselves
great because this wasn't bad enough
Right through the wall!
So what if you can use a sword?
Weapons left!
Did he just
A little cut from a dead guy
Ain't gonna kill me
Stay down already That guy's
different He's a lot tougher
than those knuckleheads we
beat the crap out of earlier
Now you will know real terror You'll see
what makes a zombie truly frightening Hey,
why are you way over there?
They don't feel even a hint of pain.
They never get tired!
And these zombie generals offer even more.
They all made quite a name
for themselves in battle?
Before they died and were
brought back to life.
Among them are a knight.
A wicked criminal. A samurai.
A pirate.
And also a gunslinger.
Just imagine the possibilities!
These ruthless fighters combined with
the relentless power of the undead.
Not a single member of your crew
is going to escape this place.
Give up.
You're done
Wall zombie
He locked us in here.
Then we can only move forward, but
speaking from experience
of fighting one zombie
general I'd say we're in
pretty deep crap here.
There's armor guides
everywhere trying to take
down these corpses one at
a time doesn't seem like
the way to go but trying
to take them on all at
once seems like an even
dumber idea this ain't good.
Yeah you got a point and this
isn't even the fight we came
in here for if we somehow manage
to escape this hall will most
likely end about side in the
courtyard right and let's split up
and meet there be careful I don't
want anyone else to disappear.
Got it got it.
Thirty-six Colubo Feetus!
That move! Zoro!
Scars on the back are the
shame of the Swordsman, but...
I've got scars on my entire body.
You look different, but
you are Zoro, right?
Call me dumber!
They're still coming!
I know what'll stop him!
Fresh fire!
Prepare the bucket!
No way!
How about some unsafe lures?
And slam!
Where's Luffy?
It looks like he wasn't
able to make it out.
I don't see him anywhere.
Probably because he's wearing that stupid
armor He blends it with the rest of them
Unless wait, you don't
think he disappeared too.
Do you it's not a good
idea to wait and find
out the zombies will
catch up to us any second
Master!
Open up this box, Lydia!
Is that a coffin?
You're gonna regret that!
That voice...
It's looping!
Wait, you mean Straw Hat's
inside of that thing?
Come on, Robin, after it!
Right!
What are you doing in that box, dumbass?
Why'd you go and get
yourself caught like that?
Hey, Straw Hat!
That's far enough!
Hey, hey!
Monkey, monkey, monkey!
All those stories you've heard about
spider monkeys, you're looking at one!
That's me!
A giant spider!
Even for a monkey, that's damn big!
It's a monster!
I'm warning you!
Let me act this monster out!
Ah!
Got another one!
Sounds like it hit the floor!
Damn it!
What are you punks gonna do to him?
Oh, don't worry.
You'll find out soon enough
since you're gonna be next.
But I'd be more worried
about myself if I were you.
You've got me in front of you, and almond
warrior zombies closing in from behind.
There's no escape.
Prepare for annihilation!